mytscstore.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy | Tractor Supply Co.

  1. Our Customer Pledge
  2. Collection and Use of Personal Information
  3. Tractor Supply's Additional Use of Personal Information
  4. Privacy Preferences/Opt-Out
  5. Access to Personal Information
  6. California Privacy Rights
  7. Children's Privacy Policy
  8. Security Limitations
  9. Security Questions or Comments
  10. How to Contact Tractor Supply
  11. Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement

We at Tractor Supply Company, including our affiliated and subsidiary companies (collectively " ** _Tractor Supply_** ") protect the personal information you provide us in accordance with this Privacy and Security Policy (" **Privacy Policy** "). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to let you know how we collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage the personal information you provide to us at any of our Tractor Supply stores (the " ** _Stores_** "), through any Tractor Supply Customer Call Centers (the " ** _Customer Call Centers_** "), through the tractorsupply.com website and other sites that may be established by Tractor Supply (the " ** _Sites_** ").

When you provide personal information at our Stores, to our Customer Call Centers, or through our Sites or email, you are consenting to the manner in which Tractor Supply will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your personal information, as described below. Tractor Supply does engage third party service providers (" ** _Service Providers_** ") with whom your information may be shared. Service Providers have their own security policies and Tractor Supply is not responsible for their conduct. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any current, updated and new products and services shall be subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms and Conditions of Use (“ ** _Terms and Conditions_** ”). By using the services provided at the Stores or the Customer Call Centers or by using the Sites you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

Tractor Supply cares about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please email us at [websupport@tractorsupply.com](mailto:websupport@tractorsupply.com)

 **A. Our Customer Pledge** (back to top)

Tractor Supply will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **B. Collection and Use of Personal Information** (back to top)

Tractor Supply may collect and use personal information that you provide us when you:

  * Purchase, order, return, exchange or request certain information about Tractor Supply's products and services;
  * Request warranty or tax exempt information;
  * Contact a Customer Call Center or customer service desk;
  * Visit, register on, or participate in the features of one of Tractor Supply's Sites, such as a bulletin board or community;
  * Enter into a contest or sweepstakes or respond to one of Tractor Supply's surveys;
  * Provide Tractor Supply with comments or suggestions;
  * Provide Tractor Supply with any information contributed to our Sites on your behalf; or
  * Provide Tractor Supply other contact information.

When you use one of our Sites or communicate with us by email, certain additional information is collected without you being prompted to provide it. This information includes, but is not limited to, non-personally-identifiable information such as IP address, cookies, profile information, click tracking and tracer tags, which are covered below. This data is used to improve the website services, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Tractor Supply will not use the information collected to market directly to that person. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to Users. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

 **1\. Shopping at Tractor Supply Company  
** When you purchase products and services at one of Tractor Supply's Stores, you may do so anonymously when you pay with cash. If you use a credit or debit card for any of your purchases, whether on a Site or in a Store, Tractor Supply will collect your credit or debit card information and keep a history of your purchases. Tractor Supply uses this information to process your orders, to ensure proper delivery, to better assist you when you visit or call us as well as to improve our product and service offerings.

When you return previously purchased merchandise or request a refund or exchange, you may be asked to give your name, address, telephone number and provide other information that identifies you, such as your driver's license. Tractor Supply collects this information to help prevent fraud.

 **2\. Customer Call Centers  
** When you call one of Tractor Supply's Customer Call Centers about a product, delivery, an installation, a billing question or for customer service, you may be asked for information that identifies you along with additional information we need to help us promptly answer your questions, such as your name, email information, mailing address and a telephone number where we might contact you. Tractor Supply may retain this information to assist you in the future or for its other business needs.

 **3\. Online Registration  
** (a) _Information Tractor Supply Requests._ Registration is an optional service provided by Tractor Supply through its Sites. You do not have to register to browse or shop online. When you register, you are asked for certain personal information which may be used to assist us in our provision of services.

(b) _Newsletters._ When you register, you will have the opportunity to receive future marketing information from Tractor Supply and to sign up for email newsletters that cover certain subjects that are of interest to you. These newsletters will be sent to you only if you choose to place your name on our mailing list. In order for us to deliver these newsletters, Tractor Supply may need to pass along your name and email address to the Service Providers who supply us with email service and who authenticate and validate the information you provide.

(c) _Updating Your Profile._ If you need to view, change, update or delete any of your registration information, log in and click "My Account" at the top of the screen. You will be taken to a page where you can access your information so that you can edit it. For more, see our section entitled "Access to Personal Information."

 **4\. Contests, Questions or Surveys  
** When you ask a question, participate in a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes at a Store, a Tractor Supply sponsored event or through our Sites, we may collect your personal information. This information is used to administer your participation in a contest or sweepstakes.

 **5\. Extended Warranty Services  
** If you purchase a Tractor Supply Extended Warranty Service, you will be required to provide personal information to third party Service Providers.

 **6\. Non-Voluntary Information  
** _(a) General Tracking Information._ Tractor Supply keeps records of the pages visited by each site user. Tractor Supply aggregates this information with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. Tractor Supply uses this information to improve its Sites and to develop functions and user tools which will make it more responsive to the needs and preferences of Tractor Supply customers.

 _(b) Cookies._ Tractor Supply Sites use a technology called "cookies" to help facilitate transactions on the Sites. A cookie is an element of software code that Tractor Supply Sites can send to your browser, which is then stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. All pages on our Sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. If you have registered with our Sites, these cookies: (1) may let us know who you are; (2) are necessary to access the personal information previously provided to us by you in order to deliver products and personalized services; and (3) will provide us and our Service Providers with information that we will use to personalize our Sites in accordance with your preferences. Should you decide not to accept cookies from our Sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Site.

 _(c) Tracer Tags._ Tractor Supply's Sites may use a technology called "tracer tags", which may also be referred to as "Clear GIFs" or "Web Beacons". This technology allows us to identify which pages you visit on our Sites. These tags are used by us to help optimize and update our Sites for you and other future website visitors.

 _(d) Other Information._ We may collect additional automatic information about your visit to our Site, such as time of day, browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. This information is used for analytical purposes and to help us provide services to our customers. We may also use this information to administer and troubleshoot our Sites.

 _(e) Aggregate Information._ On occasion we may provide this aggregate information (which shall not include personally identifiable information) to vendors, investors, potential advertisers, or news agencies to demonstrate the amount of interest in our Site and to help us plan for technical infrastructure requirements.

 **C. Tractor Supply's Additional Use of Personal Information** (back to top)

 **1\. Research and Marketing  
** In the U.S., to better serve you, we may combine the personal information that you provide with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our marketing partners and others. Tractor Supply uses that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

 **2\. Third Party Products  
** We may share personal information about Tractor Supply consumers with third parties in order to provide you with tailored information about products and services and special offers. These Service Providers also have their own privacy statement that sets out the manner in which they will collect, use and disclose personal information.

 **3\. Service Providers  
** Some of our operations, such as our Customer Call Centers, may be managed by unaffiliated companies. These companies may have access to your personal information on a confidential basis only to the extent necessary to perform their functions.

 **4\. Shipping  
** If your purchases are being shipped to you, we will share your shipping information with our delivery Service Providers (United Parcel Service, FedEx, U.S. Postal Service, or other delivery companies we select).

 **5\. Sale of Business  
** Tractor Supply reserves the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party acquirer.

 **6\. Legal Disclosure  
** Tractor Supply must provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by law.

 **7\. Third Party Links and Data  
** Tractor Supply's Sites may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. The inclusion of any link does not imply Tractor Supply's endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we encourage you to read carefully. We have no control over such websites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal information. Third party Service Providers may need access to some of your personal information. In such cases, we only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We may also provide your information to our affiliated companies and successors. We reserve the right to provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our clients, traffic patterns and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns, but does not contain personally identifiable information about any individual user.

 **8\. Secure Shopping  
** When you place orders on a Site, your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology works with your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our server.

 **D. Privacy Preferences/Opt-Out** (back to top)

If at anytime you would like to be removed from any/all Tractor Supply marketing lists, newsletters, distribution lists, or the like, you may do so by contacting us in any of the ways identified in Section J of this page. Registered site users may log onto their account at TractorSupply.com to change your privacy preferences or opt-out.

 **E. Access to Personal Information** (back to top)

As a registered user with our Sites, you can access your profile information at any time by:

  * Clicking on the "Sign In" (link) button at the top of any page on the Sites on which you registered, then
  * Clicking on the "Your Account" (link) button on the page header or on the "Your Account" link under Customer Support.

For further instructions on accessing the personal information that Tractor Supply may have about you, please see the "How to Contact Tractor Supply" Section (Section J) of this Privacy and Security Statement.

 **F. California Privacy Rights** (back to top)

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Tractor Supply pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us pursuant to any method identified in Section J.

 **G. Children's Privacy Policy** (back to top)

Please do not allow children under the age of 18 to purchase any goods through the Sites. Tractor Supply does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 through the Tractor Supply Sites. All children under the age of 13 are not permitted to provide any personally identifiable information or participate in programs or communities related to our Sites. If we determine that a child under 13 has provided personal information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information as soon as practical. If you become aware that such information has been provided by a child under 13, please notify us by contacting a Tractor Supply Customer Call Center in any of the ways identified in Section J. Please be certain to include in the subject line Privacy Policy Request

 **H. Security Limitations** (back to top)

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Tractor Supply cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us on our Sites.

 **I. Security Questions or Comments** (back to top)

If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us in any one of the ways identified in Section J.

 **J. How to Contact Tractor Supply.** (back to top)  
You may contact us in one of the following ways:

1\. Send an e-mail to: customerservice@tractorsupply.com

2\. Call 1-877-718-6750;

3\. Send your request by mail to:

Tractor Supply Company  
200 Powell Place  
Brentwood, TN 37027  
ATTN: Internet Customer Service

4\. Fill out a comment form online now. _[Click here to go to Contact Us comment form.](http://www.tractorsupply.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/ContactUsForm?langId=-1&storeId=10551&catalogId=10001)_

 **K. Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement** (back to top)

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any updates to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Continued use of our Sites, Stores, Customer Call Centers or other Tractor Supply services following our posting of the change notice or an updated Privacy Policy will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.

Last update: February 14, 2011

Copyright © 2013 Tractor Supply Company, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
